Hello everyone, I'm here again.
It's a Friday night again, and you're still in our live stream.
I'm still your teacher, Molly.
Molly has been a bit angry lately, and she has a sore throat.
Maybe she won't be able to speak clearly today, so I'll have to forgive her.
Why are there still people laughing at me?
Give the teacher some tea. Thank you, our little C-Jun, for giving me some tea.
Thank you.
Today, we're mainly going to make a suit, and then we'll have time for our dishes.
What we're making today is a lady's suit.
I believe you've already gotten our materials.
If you don't have the materials, you can follow our WeChat official account, Clos3D.
You can get our live material by replying to the link in the background.
Now, we're going to make this suit.
We're making a lady's suit today.
First, you can open a model of a girl from the Elta folder,
and then import the material into our project.
Let's close the window of the library.
Now, we can see that there's only one half of this model.
We need to match and copy the other half of it.
First, we use the adjustment tool to select the sleeve and the back of the model.
Then, on any model, right-click,
in the menu, there's a horizontal panel, a panel, and a seam line at the bottom of the column.
Press the shortcut key, Ctrl-D.
We choose this option, and then press the Shift key,
and place it horizontally to the other side.
Click on the blank to place the panel.
For the front panel, we don't need to match and copy it.
Now, in the 3D window,
click on Edit 2D Arrangement Places All,
and move our 2D arrangement to the 3D window.
Then, in the 3D vertical tool bar,
select the fourth one,
and then select the third one to display the arrangement points.
You can also press the shortcut key, Shift-JF,
to display the arrangement points.
Now, we select all the panels in the frame,
and then right-click on any panel in the 3D window,
press the left button,
and move the mouse to move the panel to the top of the model.
Then, click on the blank to cancel the selection.
Now, we're going to arrange the panels.
Since our panel and the front panel have a layer relationship,
the panel is at the bottom of the panel.
So, we're going to use the positioning tool here
to move the panel to the bottom of the front panel.
We don't need to move it too far,
just move it closer to the panel.
After moving the panel,
select the three panels in the 2D window,
and then press the shortcut key, Ctrl-D,
and then press the Shift-JF,
to move the panel to the other side.
Now, the front panel has been aligned.
And since we've just arranged the layers,
we don't need to arrange the layers again.
After aligning the panels,
we need to do another layer arrangement.
Since the front panel needs to be twisted,
the front panel needs to be twisted,
and so does the front panel.
This is a female suit,
so the right panel should be at the top of the left panel.
On the right panel,
we need to press Shift-JF,
select the front panel,
the right panel,
and the right panel.
Then, on the panel,
press the shortcut key,
and select the positioning tool.
Use the positioning tool
to move the right panel to the top of the left panel.
We can rotate the view
to see their layers.
Now, in the 3D window,
we move the mouse to the back panel.
The back panel has a gap.
There is a layer relationship between them.
On the right panel,
we press the shortcut key on the left panel,
and select the positioning tool.
We move the left panel to the top of the right panel.
Then, on the right panel,
we move the mouse to the top of the left panel.
we move the mouse to the top of the right panel.
Then, we rotate the view
to see the layers between them.
If you press the blank button,
you can cancel the selection.
We're now going to arrange the panels.
Arrange the panels on the model.
created using vectorite
You can press the shortcut key 2
to rotate the view to the right-front view.
We're going to press Shift here.
Select the two panels
right and left.
Then move the mouse to the 3D window virtual model arrangement point, click the arrangement point, and put the board down.
Because we have done the layer arrangement before, so when we are arranging the board, there is also a layer relationship between them.
Let's arrange the front side to the model.
We can adjust the position of the board by adjusting the position of the X-axis and Y-axis in the purple list arranged in the attribute editor.
Then we rotate the view to place its sleeves, large sleeves and small sleeves.
Rotate to the back view to arrange its back.
We also press the button.
Press the button at the same time, select the back two left and right, place it on the model arrangement point, arrange its back.
We can also adjust the position of the board by adjusting the number of the x-axis in the purple list.
Finally, arrange the curtain.
Place the curtain at the view point.
Once we have arranged it,
You can press Shift-JF to hide it.
Now, let's start sewing.
Let's use the sewing tool first.
You can also press the shortcut N
to sew the front and back of it.
When sewing,
you need to pay attention to the direction of the sewing line.
They all need to be the same.
If the sewing line is in the opposite direction,
we can use the edge sewing tool
to press the right-hand button on the sewing line
and select the switch sewing line
from the menu.
Then we continue to sew.
In this case, the에
The sewing method is almost the same as in 2D-objet twin tosses.
We will go back to the sewing line
and start working on a newly created sewing line.
Let's start the sewing by disconnecting the snipers on eachHarmonizer.
Now let's start sewing the sleeves.
We also sew the sleeves facing the blade.
When sewing, we also need to pay attention to the sewing line direction.
If you don't know the sewing line direction,
you can check the sewing line direction through the 3D window,
to see if it is correct.
We can pull the sleeves down a little.
If the sewing line direction is wrong,
we choose the wrong sewing line.
Right-click on the sewing line,
and choose to change the sewing line.
Now let's sew the collar.
First, we use the sewing machine for sewing the collar.
Then we use the free sewing tool to sew the face to the body.
To sew these sewing lines to the body, we need to change the type of sewing line in the parameter editor to Tend.
This way, after the simulation, the sewing line between the body and the face will be smoother.
After the sewing is done, we can rotate the 3D window to check if the sewing line type is correct.
Now let's add a button on the front.
We choose the button tool.
Add a button on the left front.
Because we have two layers, there is also a hanging surface.
So we use the move button tool.
On the button we just added,
select these two buttons.
On any button, right-click.
There is a layer to set the sewing line in the menu.
Select the layer to set the sewing line.
Change the sewing line layer to 2.
Then click OK.
Now we can see a cross here.
We can use the move tool to move its position.
After determining the position, we select these two buttons again.
The two buttons.
On the button on the right, click.
We have a layer to set the sewing line in the menu.
We choose this option.
Now we can see that it also has these two two lines.
And it also automatically sets the sewing line as 2.
We can also select these two positions here.
and select the move button to move its position.
Oh, someone asked if today is the basic class?
Yes, this time is still the basic class.
How long has the live stream been?
We just live streamed for 13 minutes.
We usually live stream once every two weeks.
The live stream time is at 8 pm on Friday.
After the button has been fixed,
we select the button to close the button.
First, we close the button,
then put the arrow to the left of the button.
Then we can close the button.
After we close the button,
we return the button to the move button.
Now,
we open the button.
Finally, we open the button.
We open the model.
Then we close the model.
We select this one in the 2D window.
We select this one.
In the attribute editor,
there is a thin layer at the bottom.
We open this triangle.
We close the
and we will jump to a preview.
We select the last one in the preview.
Here, if you have a closer look at our 5.2 live stream,
you will find that there is a detailed guide here.
Then we select the last one.
Then we open the model.
We apply this to this costume.
Then we close the model.
We open the window again.
Open the window.
Double click on the avatar folder.
From this file,
here,
select this model.
Double click on the folder where the model is.
Open the pose folder.
Here,
we select this pose called 03.
Double click on it.
Then click OK.
Change the model's posture to a vertical one.
Next, we are going to make its
back opening and turning.
We are going to make the back opening first.
Rotate the 3D view to the back view.
You can also press the shortcut key.
Then rotate it.
Just zoom it in.
In the 2D window,
we select the circle outline tool.
You can also press the shortcut key.
To make the selection.
Here, we select.
On the back view,
we can see a blue base line.
We select this base line.
Press the return key.
We can make the selection as the internal line.
Then click on the blank.
Cancel the selection.
Because these two back views are
linked versions.
So when we select
the base line of one of the versions,
the other version will also
be selected together.
But because we only need
the base line of the left back view,
we don't need the base line of the right back view.
So what do we do now?
We can click on the right button
on any of the two back views.
There is a release link
at the bottom of the face-to-face version.
We select the release link.
Remove the link of the two versions.
Then select.
Left.
Then select the base line of the right back view.
This internal line.
Then press delete.
Delete it.
That's it.
Then we select the folding arrangement tool
in the 3D tool bar.
Select this base line.
Select this base line on the 3D shape.
Then select the direction of the arrow
to fold it.
After folding,
we will set the folding angle
of this internal line in the 2D window.
Set it to 0 degrees.
Then we use the sewing tool
to sew it together.
We select the line sewing tool.
Here we need to pay attention
to its sewing line direction.
It needs to be relative.
After sewing,
we also need to
change the sewing line type
to the sewing line type
of the line.
Then we use the free sewing line tool again.
Sew the two ends of the bottom.
Then we sew the two ends of the bottom.
The sewing line direction is also relative.
The sewing line type also needs to be changed.
After making,
we press the model again.
Then this back view is made.
Now we can open the back view and take a look at it.
Then we can open the back view and take a look at it.
How to distinguish between 0° and 180°?
It's easy to distinguish.
First, we can distinguish it by color.
We use the filter tool to filter out another inner line.
Here we can see that the inner line of 0° is red.
The color of the inner line of 180° is a brownish red.
Now let's see how to flip it over.
We have a replay.
You can follow our WeChat official account to get our replays.
How many more times do we have to stream?
You can follow our WeChat official account to get our live streams.
Now let's flip it over.
We also use the filter tool to do so.
Select the flip line on the upper body and the one on the top.
Then select the flip line on the collar.
Press the return button.
Then you can filter it into the inner line.
After filtering, we also use the tool to do the folding.
We can first select the inner line on the inside.
Then we can flip it over according to the direction of the arrow.
Here, we need to adjust itsjo 對啊
to 360 degrees.
We should be able to continue with the same process in the first one.
And then let's start to´ Departure of Percussion'sloophilic shoulder line.
Now select the place in which we will Spare your shoulder line.
Then let's select the surfal line and give her a motor.
Then, rotate the corner to rotate this curve on the surface, and also rotate it.
Here, we need to pay attention that the two corners should not touch each other.
Let's rotate the other side.
Also, we need to adjust the angle of these two curves to 360 degrees.
After adjusting, let's simulate.
If you have such a shaking situation, you can press Ctrl-Z to retract it.
Then, select the move tool, select the face, and press the right button on the large panel.
Press the right button on the large panel.
Then, there is a hardening, and the shortcut key is Ctrl-Z-F.
We can temporarily harden it to make its material temporarily hard.
Then, simulate it again.
After that, let's select these hardening versions.
Press the right button to undo the hardening.
You can also press the shortcut key, Ctrl-Z-H.
Press the right button to undo the hardening. You can also press the shortcut key, Ctrl-Z-F.
Press the right button to undo the hardening. You can also press the shortcut key, Ctrl-Z-H.
From this status, you can turn your model to continue the rotation.
If your model simply cannot turn 내模,
You could use the
collection system to brake it and ю
You could also add a fixed speed.
you could use the
collection system to brake it and ю
Toassing down the пад Year
To
To için
To Over
左右
We can use the same method for the other side as well.
Press W and click on the board to create a fixed point.
We can adjust the position of the fixed point to adjust its shape.
Once we're set.
Come on guys function also works,
when you click on it on the next page,
go ahead and show the face.
This time let's say we show our topic.
If you want to share your description,
In the library window, drag the document house to the bottom.
Give it a wool fabric.
Drag it.
Put it in the fabric1 of the object window.
Then release the mouse.
That's it.
Then open the simulation.
Apply the fabric to this 3D costume.
Then close the simulation.
Next, let's make it an embroidery strip.
Oh, it's a shoulder strip.
I'm sorry.
Embroidery strip.
We can use the 2D window.
On this multi-layered tool,
left click on the scene.
Then there will be a
a
tool bar.
We select the rectangle.
The shortcut key is S.
After selecting,
we left-click on the blank area.
Here we need to set its size.
How do we know its size?
We choose to cancel first.
We use the editor tool.
We choose the sleeves.
The top of the sleeve.
These few lines.
We can select them at the same time by pressing Shift.
We can.
At the bottom of the selected line at the edge of the mouse,
you can see a 2D line length.
Its length is 447.9 mm.
Then we select the rectangle tool again here.
Left-click on the blank area.
On this triangle,
we enter the width of the rectangle.
The width is 447.9 mm.
The height is 10 mm.
Right-click on it.
And then we press OK.
That's how we create a...
this rectangle.
.
and place it on the top of the sleeve.
Then select the free sewing tool
and sew the rectangle to the sleeve.
Here we need to press Shift
to do a 1 to n line of sewing.
After sewing, we release Shift.
Here we also need to pay attention to the direction of the sewing line.
After sewing, we select the adjustment panel tool.
On this rectangle panel, select it.
Right-click on it and select face panel, panel, and sewing line.
Then press Shift to level it and place it on the other side.
After placing it, we can press Shift to select these two.
Oh, sorry, the text is 477.
.
This is 477.9, and I made it short here, so we can make it longer by 35.
We can use the Edit Format Tool to check its format.
After that, we select these two panels at the same time as we press Shift.
Then right-click on the 3D window panel,
and add it to the Input menu.
We choose this option, and add it to the Input menu.
Here, before we simulate, we need to select this Transform,
and change its particle diameter to 5,
and its thickness to 4.
After we're done, we open the simulation.
As you can see, there's a bulge here.
Next, we're going to add its...
Before we make the switch, we're going to improve its quality.
Here, we set its particle diameter to 10,
and its thickness to 1.
Here, we need to change its usage range to 1 to 2.5,
or 1 to 3.
Because we just set the particle diameter to 4,
we can't change its thickness to 4.
So here, we change its usage range to 1 to 3,
and click OK.
Then we open the simulation,
and apply the settings we just changed
to the 3D costume.
After we're done with the simulation,
we open the simulation again.
We need to change the particle diameter to 5.
After we're done,
we go to the top left corner of the simulation.
We'll go to the
library window.
We found the article house from Hardware and Tremes.
Open the file.
Find Shudder,
this file house.
You can open it with the file, too.
There are four outlets here.
Let's choose this 4mm woman.
Open the camera.
Do you want to save it? Click No.
Here, we need to click Add.
If we click Open, the suit we just made will disappear.
Then click Confirm.
Since it is a clothing document,
although it doesn't have a virtual model, it has the size of a virtual model.
We don't need to increase the size of its posture and the size of the virtual model.
Click No.
Here, we can see that it has added two pads.
Now, we add this pad to the window and drag it down to the vicinity of the whole panel.
In the 2D window, we click the 2nd shortcut.
Then zoom in and move it.
Then use the positioning tool to drag it down to the vicinity of the shoulder.
Then click the 4th shortcut to rotate its angle to the side angle.
Again, use the positioning tool to move it.
After moving it,
we
right-click.
Let's freeze it.
The shortcut is Ctrl and K.
After freezing it, we select all the clothing versions.
Note that it is all the clothing versions.
Then set its level to 1.
Then press Return.
Click Confirm.
Then open the simulation.
After the simulation is completed, we close the simulation again.
Then set the level of all the clothing versions to 0.
After this, we open the simulation again.
Then select the keyframe.
Then right-click.
There is a freeze button.
The shortcut is Ctrl and K.
After the freeze, we can see that it is all the clothing versions.
Then click the 4th shortcut to move it.
Again, use the positioning tool to drag it down to the vicinity of the shoulder.
Open the simulation again.
Then we open the simulation again.
Then click the 4th shortcut to move it.
Then press Return.
Hop on the touche.
Then we finally measure the length.
Then our shoulder is reflected.
Thejas purple 로 прост lights
yellow square
gray square
Next.
In the link we see the part that explains re-trimming.
At this point, the red square is not ready.
Let's re-trim the white paper.
We Steuer is already in the process.
This is operation.
Last week, we made a pair of pants and a pair of T-shirts.
This week, we added this suit jacket outside the original pair of T-shirts.
We can open the T-shirt and pants file we made last time.
We double-click to open it.
We double-click to add a new type of T-shirt.
We don't need to double-click to open the T-shirt.
We can move the T-shirt to the top of the T-shirt.
We can click to cancel the selection.
Now, we need to cross-select all the suit covers and test.
We can cross-select and click the selected cover,
we can see it in the preferred menu.
We can select it to be the group.
Now when I choose to select any of the 완 Physical Cool culture tops of the group visos.
We can select all of them.
On the selected version, click on the button at the 3D window,
and press Ctrl-J to activate the version.
After that, we can click on the button again on the costume,
and hide the 3D version.
Press Shift-Q to activate the version.
When will the teacher explain the production of the sweater?
You can pay attention to this in the next video.
Now let's put the sweater into the pants.
You can also select all the sweater versions.
You can also right-click to group them.
You can also right-click to group the pants versions.
In this way, when we select any version,
the entire group version will be selected.
Let's select the shirt version,
and give it a layer setting of "-1".
Then click on OK.
Then open the model.
Then the sweater will be put into the pants.
After the model is stable,
we turn off the model.
Then select the shirt version again.
The shirt version of the T-shirt will be set to "-0".
Then click on OK.
Open the model again.
We can see that it is still stable.
Because our system can automatically remember the order they set.
Now let's put the sweater into the pants.
First of all, we are in the 3D window.
In the 3D window,
in the tool bar,
we select the second option,
which is display 3D clothing.
We select display clothing.
The shortcut key is
shift plus W.
The sweater that has just been hidden
will be displayed.
It is still in the state of fire.
Now we can rotate the view.
We can see that this T-shirt
is partly outside the sweater.
We need it to be inside the sweater.
In order to make the model stable,
we select the T-shirt version first.
Then at the bottom of the model editor,
there is a vertex slider.
Let's give it a vertex slider first.
Let's set the vertex slider to 90.
Then we simulate it.
We can see that it has a little bit of shrinkage.
But there is still a part outside.
Let's close the simulation.
We set its shrinkage to 80.
Then open the simulation again.
Now we can see that most of it
is already inside.
Then we close the simulation here.
Then we select all the T-shirt versions.
Because we set the group,
we select any version of the group.
In this way,
all the T-shirt versions will be selected.
We click on the right button of the 3D window
to turn it on.
The shortcut is Ctrl-J.
After that,
we set it to a layer.
We set its layer to 1.
Then click OK.
Then continue to open the simulation here.
After the simulation is stable,
we close the simulation.
We select this T-shirt version again.
Set its layer to 0.
Because here we can see that
its suit is not wearing a shirt.
We can select any.
We can select the T-shirt version.
Then use the positioning tool to move it.
Then we can select the T-shirt version.
After we move it to the right position,
we open the simulation again.
We can see that
its button is shaking.
Then we can select these two buttons
and click on Shift.
Select these two buttons at the same time.
Close the collision between them.
In this way,
our simulation will be more stable.
Then we can close the simulation.
Next,
let's talk about the gluten.
What is gluten?
Gluten is a new feature.
Yes, gluten is a new feature.
You have to focus on
what you need to do with gluten.
On the top of the board,
there is a gluten button.
We can remove gluten first.
There is a gluten in here.
Let's choose the group.
This is the group version.
This is the new feature of 5.2.
We can choose this T-shirt version
because we just gave it an image shrink.
Let's turn on the model.
Now let's set its image shrink to 100%.
But since we just set it to 80%,
we need to set it a little bit.
Let's set it to 90% and press the return button.
Let it slowly simulate.
Then let's set it to 100%.
Once it's stable, we can see this button.
We can press the left button on the button.
But there will be a positional ball.
We can use the positional ball tool to move this button.
Once you open it, you can click on the simulation.
Then this button will be stable.
Let's set it to 100%.
Since our T-shirt is usually double-layered,
we need to increase its thickness.
We can choose this fabric at the door of the house.
Then there is a thickness of 1.06 at the bottom of the model.
We click on this.
We can set this one.
Because we just set the group function,
we can set it to 100%.
So we set the double-layer on this panel.
We can select this panel separately.
We increase it to a thickness of 1.
And we can pull the mouse to the top.
Remember a double-layer.
This way we can see that this collar is double-layered.
Then we press the shortcut 2 to select it to the front view.
We can click on this fabric first.
Then we open the triangle in the pattern.
Click on the fill pattern.
Then click on this color.
We can use its small tube tool to absorb its color here.
We can also enter RGB values here.
You can also select it in the panning color bar next to it.
After selecting the color,
we can select the increase button on the left here.
Increase.
In this way, this color will be added to this color board.
Click on OK.
Then we can also add a color to this pants.
If we can't find the fabric used in its pants here,
we can click on this pants panel in the 2D window.
The corresponding fabric in the 3D window,
its font will be a bright blue font.
Then we click on the color.
We can add the color we just added.
Click on this color that will be added.
Click on it like this.
You can use it directly.
Just click on OK.
There are also buttons and buttons.
We select the button.
In the 3D window,
select the button.
Then in the color editor,
we can change its shape.
We can change its shape to a square shape.
Then we can change its type to plastic.
Of course, you can also choose
metal or other types.
Here you can choose.
If you need,
you can add a texture to this place.
Then click on this color.
We can also use this color
that we just added to the color board.
You can also make it.
You can also use other colors.
You can choose from the actual funz color box.
Choose the color you think is suitable
Then click with
You can also use other colors.
You can use other colors.
Just click OK.
Then we will select by,
select .
You can also customize its shape
in theanda v messy.
You can also master how wide it is.
Change its type to sheep color.
如果大家对钮扣有特殊需求,需要自己制作钮扣的话呢,可以参考我们之前的直播,我们有讲过如何自定义钮扣。
After the process is completed, we will give it a clothing quality check.
Here, we need to reduce the usage range to 1, and then change its particle diameter to 5, and then click OK.
The number that we have just set up can now be applied to the actual clothes.
After the situation is delivered, we will click on the gear button to apply the settings we have just set up to this single-place clothing.
Here, we can see that the item is finished.
Let's close the machine.
This is how the dress is done.
You can see two red pins here.
If you don't want to see this pin,
you can choose the second row of the vertical tool bar at the window of our 3D clothing.
Then there is a display.
Click on this option and the display will be hidden.
There are also these blue base lines and red internal lines on the clothing.
You can also display the internal line and display the base line in the 3D clothing option.
Turn off these two options.
This way, the base line and internal line on the clothing are hidden.
We are almost done.
Please stay tuned for our next video.
Next, let's move on to our last topic.
It is about
some settings for rendering.
We can choose to render in the menu bar.
There is a render tool.
Click on render.
Here, we can choose the first one,
to render at the same time.
Click on it.
Click on it,
then press .
Press .
Then press .
In this way, our 3D clothing will be shown at the same time in this rendering window, no matter what view you choose, it will be displayed at the same time.
If you need to pause, you can choose the third one to stop rendering.
Next, I will talk about some of our basic rendering settings.
There is a picture next to the render window.
Click on it.
This is a picture video attribute.
In the attribute editor, we can choose a picture or a rotating picture or animation.
The animation can be selected from our last live stream.
Select the view from the 3D window.
There are two view modes, the current view and the custom view.
If we choose the custom view, we can press the right button in the blank space of the 3D window.
There is a custom view, which is the user view.
We can choose a suitable rendering view.
Then click here.
Click the button on the top right corner of the screen to add the current view.
You can add this view to this one.
Then we can rotate to different places and click on this one to add.
In this way, these views will be added.
If we need to use any of the views,
we double click on this view.
In this way, 3D clothing will rotate to the selected view.
Once again, we select the image video attribute.
Here, we can show all the colors.
When we create the colors in the color mode,
we can click on this one.
It will show all the colors.
In the bottom, we can choose the size of the image.
There are many sizes to choose from.
You can also change them.
Generally, the size of A4 is enough.
We can also choose the direction of the image,
whether it is vertical or horizontal.
We can set the resolution to 300.
We can also set the background color.
Here, we can see the different background colors.
If we don't need a background,
we can choose the texture.
If we don't need any color or background,
we can set it to transparency.
Click on transparency.
If we need a stage background,
we can add a texture.
We can also set a 3D background in the 3D window.
So here are our 3D backgrounds.
Next, here are the keep file names or user names.
Here is the keep path.
For image format, you can choose png or jpg.
Next, this is HTML.
We already mentioned it in our 5.2 live broadcast.
If everyone is interested,
please check out our replay video.
Let's go back to the tool bar in the rendering page.
There is a light attribute next to the image video attribute.
This is the light button.
We click on this button.
Here we can see that there are multiple lights.
We usually use the top light.
Here, in the environment, we click on this little button.
Here we can see that there are multiple lights.
We can choose different lights according to our needs.
Then click OK.
We can adjust the brightness of this light by adjusting the brightness of the light.
The light angle is the angle needed for this light.
The light is the angle used to adjust the brightness of the screen.
The light is used to adjust the brightness of the 3D window.
You can select the light in the shape of a center.
You can choose the light in the shape of a center.
Can you explain the camera properties in detail?
This can follow our follow-up live broadcast.
Here, I have shown the different lighting in these environmental pictures, which you can refer to.
This picture is lighting 1.
This is lighting 2. You can clearly see the contrast of lighting.
This is lighting 3. This is lighting 4.
This is lighting 5. This is lighting 6.
This is lighting 7.
This is a high contrast, low contrast, and medium contrast.
This is a lighting used in animation.
You can choose the lighting you need according to your needs.
This is lighting 4.
This is lighting 5.
This is lighting 6.
Next, let's see the Q&A section.
Do you have any questions?
You can ask your questions in the live chat.
Thank you.
大家还有什么问题吗?
今天有笑场,对不起
Use your own model to adjust it to a company model.
If you have data, you can use the virtual model editor to directly enter its value here.
If you are a scan model, you can use the virtual model editor to convert it to virtual model.
Where is the streamer? The streamer is here.
Ms. Moly has been here all the time.
What will the streaming view look like?
If you drop your pants, you can check if the streaming view is not increased.
We need to increase the streaming view on the waist of the pants.
What is the purpose of changing the list to 5?
To make it more authentic.
能分享一个18048模特的详细尺寸吗? Can you share a detailed size of a 18048 model?
这个你可以去百度上搜索 You can go to Baidu and search for it
大家还有什么别的问题吗? Do you have any other questions?
模特怎么扫描Zinc Loan? How to scan Zinc Loan?
这个我们是通过第三方公司进行扫描的 We scan Zinc Loan through a third-party company
如果你有需要的话,可以联系我们 If you need, you can contact us
我们可以给你推荐一个扫描公司 We can recommend a scanning company for you
抽者参数怎样设置合理些呢? How to set the draw parameters in a reasonable way?
这个可能需要问你们的指钥师傅 This might require your guide
增加粘称怎么调呢? How to adjust the增加粘称?
我们选中版片,然后在属性编辑器下方选中版片,然后在属性编辑器下方
增加粘称这里,让它勾选,增加粘称这里,让它勾选,
增加粘称这里,让它勾选,
然后在预设这里,可以选择这些我们有预设的这些秤, Ch confinement can also be used to select the suitable
Do we need to change the layer of the T-shape to 0 after the negative 1 simulation?
Yes, you need to change it to 0.
Otherwise, you will always be in the light.
How to contact?
What do you want to contact?
Oh, how to contact us? Sorry.
You can contact us on the official website.
You can also send us a message.
We will reply to you.
The little crystal has appeared.
Our little crystal has always been there.
We can't take it easy.
You can use our WeChat official account to get our daily live broadcast information.
Next week we will have a live broadcast with Closed Sets topic.
If you need it, you can come to listen to it.
If you have any questions, our live broadcast is called Closed Sets.
Our live stream is coming to an end
The system is wearing a headband
It's quite chubby, can you change your pose?
Our headband can change its pose
Do small bacteria have the chance to get out of the mirror?
Do you guys want small bacteria to get out of the mirror?
Two sets of clothes will always be pulled into the clothes
It may be that your layer relationship is not set well
How to set up a non-slip fabric?
It will transform in the simulation
In this case, you can use our fabric measurement machine
To input the fabric data into the system to perform the simulation
This process can be solved with your own device
Please observe our live stream
Every week is continuous
The live stream 5 clock is about the Closed South
It was raised to Dun heart
May 22, it is the current live stream
May 29, it is the current live stream
It is not a secret
how to make the details of the outfit.
I can't participate in the show without my shoes.
You can refer to our official website link.
You can search on our official website.
Do you have any questions?
If you don't have any questions,
Ms. Mo Li is going to have dinner after work.
Have you all had dinner?
If you haven't had dinner yet,
then hurry up and go.
You can follow our WeChat account.
You can get our live stream materials
by replying to the link in the background.
Do you have any questions?
You can follow our main live stream
and our Master Car series.
Ms. Mo Li's live stream
is based on the basics.
Eat durian.
I look forward to seeing you next time.
Ms. Mo Li will see you next time on 29.
You can look forward to it.
Which teacher would you like to have your live stream?
You're doing well, teacher.
Yes, tomorrow,
If you are interested, you can go check out our MD live stream.
It's also our teacher Sherry's live stream.
Thank you for watching.